export const dakutenData = [
  { "id": 1, "question": "が", "correctAnswer": "ga" },
  { "id": 2, "question": "ぎ", "correctAnswer": "gi" },
  { "id": 3, "question": "ぐ", "correctAnswer": "gu" },
  { "id": 4, "question": "げ", "correctAnswer": "ge" },
  { "id": 5, "question": "ご", "correctAnswer": "go" },
  { "id": 6, "question": "ざ", "correctAnswer": "za" },
  { "id": 7, "question": "じ", "correctAnswer": "ji" },
  { "id": 8, "question": "ず", "correctAnswer": "zu" },
  { "id": 9, "question": "ぜ", "correctAnswer": "ze" },
  { "id": 10, "question": "ぞ", "correctAnswer": "zo" },
  { "id": 11, "question": "だ", "correctAnswer": "da" },
  { "id": 12, "question": "ぢ", "correctAnswer": "ji" },
  { "id": 13, "question": "づ", "correctAnswer": "zu" },
  { "id": 14, "question": "で", "correctAnswer": "de" },
  { "id": 15, "question": "ど", "correctAnswer": "do" },
  { "id": 16, "question": "ば", "correctAnswer": "ba" },
  { "id": 17, "question": "び", "correctAnswer": "bi" },
  { "id": 18, "question": "ぶ", "correctAnswer": "bu" },
  { "id": 19, "question": "べ", "correctAnswer": "be" },
  { "id": 20, "question": "ぼ", "correctAnswer": "bo" },
  { "id": 21, "question": "ぱ", "correctAnswer": "pa" },
  { "id": 22, "question": "ぴ", "correctAnswer": "pi" },
  { "id": 23, "question": "ぷ", "correctAnswer": "pu" },
  { "id": 24, "question": "ぺ", "correctAnswer": "pe" },
  { "id": 25, "question": "ぽ", "correctAnswer": "po" },
  { "id": 26, "question": "ガ", "correctAnswer": "ga" },
  { "id": 27, "question": "ギ", "correctAnswer": "gi" },
  { "id": 28, "question": "グ", "correctAnswer": "gu" },
  { "id": 29, "question": "ゲ", "correctAnswer": "ge" },
  { "id": 30, "question": "ゴ", "correctAnswer": "go" },
  { "id": 31, "question": "ザ", "correctAnswer": "za" },
  { "id": 32, "question": "ジ", "correctAnswer": "ji" },
  { "id": 33, "question": "ズ", "correctAnswer": "zu" },
  { "id": 34, "question": "ゼ", "correctAnswer": "ze" },
  { "id": 35, "question": "ゾ", "correctAnswer": "zo" },
  { "id": 36, "question": "ダ", "correctAnswer": "da" },
  { "id": 37, "question": "ヂ", "correctAnswer": "ji" },
  { "id": 38, "question": "ヅ", "correctAnswer": "zu" },
  { "id": 39, "question": "デ", "correctAnswer": "de" },
  { "id": 40, "question": "ド", "correctAnswer": "do" },
  { "id": 41, "question": "バ", "correctAnswer": "ba" },
  { "id": 42, "question": "ビ", "correctAnswer": "bi" },
  { "id": 43, "question": "ブ", "correctAnswer": "bu" },
  { "id": 44, "question": "ベ", "correctAnswer": "be" },
  { "id": 45, "question": "ボ", "correctAnswer": "bo" },
  { "id": 46, "question": "パ", "correctAnswer": "pa" },
  { "id": 47, "question": "ピ", "correctAnswer": "pi" },
  { "id": 48, "question": "プ", "correctAnswer": "pu" },
  { "id": 49, "question": "ペ", "correctAnswer": "pe" },
  { "id": 50, "question": "ポ", "correctAnswer": "po" }
  ];
  